[
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Gombak",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Gombak LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Gombak station, the last southbound train departs at 2335H, the last northbound train departs at -, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Melati",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Melati LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taman Melati station, the last southbound train departs at 2338H, the last northbound train departs at 2442H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Wangsa Maju",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Wangsa Maju LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Wangsa Maju station, the last southbound train departs at 2341H, the last northbound train departs at 2439H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sri Rampai",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Sri Rampai LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Sri Rampai station, the last southbound train departs at 2343H, the last northbound train departs at 2437H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Setiawangsa",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Setiawangsa LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Setiawangsa station, the last southbound train departs at 2347H, the last northbound train departs at 2433H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Jelatek",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Jelatek LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Jelatek station, the last southbound train departs at 2349H, the last northbound train departs at 2431H, and the ticket counter closes at 2340H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Dato' Keramat",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Dato' Keramat LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Dato' Keramat station, the last southbound train departs at 2351H, the last northbound train departs at 2429H, and the ticket counter closes at 2340H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Damai",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Damai LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Damai station, the last southbound train departs at 2353H, the last northbound train departs at 2427H, and the ticket counter closes at 2340H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Ampang Park",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Ampang Park LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Ampang Park station, the last southbound train departs at 2355H, the last northbound train departs at 2425H, and the ticket counter closes at 2350H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "KLCC",
    "question": "What are the last train times at KLCC LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at KLCC station, the last southbound train departs at 2357H, the last northbound train departs at 2423H, and the ticket counter closes at 2350H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kampung Baru",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kampung Baru LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Kampung Baru station, the last southbound train departs at 2359H, the last northbound train departs at 2421H, and the ticket counter closes at 2355H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Dang Wangi",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Dang Wangi LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Dang Wangi station, the last southbound train departs at 2401H, the last northbound train departs at 2419H, and the ticket counter closes at 2355H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Masjid Jamek",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Masjid Jamek LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Masjid Jamek station, the last southbound train departs at 2403H, the last northbound train departs at 2417H, and the ticket counter closes at 2355H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Pasar Seni",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Pasar Seni LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Pasar Seni station, the last southbound train departs at 2405H, the last northbound train departs at 2415H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "KL Sentral",
    "question": "What are the last train times at KL Sentral LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at KL Sentral station, the last southbound train departs at 2408H, the last northbound train departs at 2412H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bangsar",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bangsar LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Bangsar station, the last southbound train departs at 2410H, the last northbound train departs at 2410H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Abdullah Hukum",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Abdullah Hukum LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Abdullah Hukum station, the last southbound train departs at 2412H, the last northbound train departs at 2408H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kerinchi",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kerinchi LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Kerinchi station, the last southbound train departs at 2414H, the last northbound train departs at 2406H, and the ticket counter closes at 2355H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Universiti",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Universiti LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Universiti station, the last southbound train departs at 2416H, the last northbound train departs at 2404H, and the ticket counter closes at 2355H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Jaya LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taman Jaya station, the last southbound train departs at 2419H, the last northbound train departs at 2401H, and the ticket counter closes at 2355H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Asia Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Asia Jaya LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Asia Jaya station, the last southbound train departs at 2421H, the last northbound train departs at 2359H, and the ticket counter closes at 2350H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Paramount",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Paramount LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taman Paramount station, the last southbound train departs at 2423H, the last northbound train departs at 2357H, and the ticket counter closes at 2350H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Bahagia",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Bahagia LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taman Bahagia station, the last southbound train departs at 2425H, the last northbound train departs at 2355H, and the ticket counter closes at 2350H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kelana Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kelana Jaya LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Kelana Jaya station, the last southbound train departs at 2428H, the last northbound train departs at 2352H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Lembah Subang",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Lembah Subang LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Lembah Subang station, the last southbound train departs at 2431H, the last northbound train departs at 2349H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Ara Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Ara Damansara LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Ara Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2433H, the last northbound train departs at 2347H, and the ticket counter closes at 2340H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Glenmarie",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Glenmarie LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Glenmarie station, the last southbound train departs at 2435H, the last northbound train departs at 2345H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Subang Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Subang Jaya LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Subang Jaya station, the last southbound train departs at 2438H, the last northbound train departs at 2342H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "SS 15",
    "question": "What are the last train times at SS 15 LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at SS 15 station, the last southbound train departs at 2441H, the last northbound train departs at 2339H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "SS 18",
    "question": "What are the last train times at SS 18 LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at SS 18 station, the last southbound train departs at 2443H, the last northbound train departs at 2337H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "USJ 7",
    "question": "What are the last train times at USJ 7 LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at USJ 7 station, the last southbound train departs at 2447H, the last northbound train departs at 2333H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taipan",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taipan LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taipan station, the last southbound train departs at 2449H, the last northbound train departs at 2331H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Wawasan",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Wawasan LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Wawasan station, the last southbound train departs at 2451H, the last northbound train departs at 2329H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "USJ 21",
    "question": "What are the last train times at USJ 21 LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at USJ 21 station, the last southbound train departs at 2453H, the last northbound train departs at 2327H, and the ticket counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Alam Megah",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Alam Megah LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Alam Megah station, the last southbound train departs at 2456H, the last northbound train departs at 2324H, and the ticket counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Subang Alam",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Subang Alam LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Subang Alam station, the last southbound train departs at 2458H, the last northbound train departs at 2322H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Putra Heights",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Putra Heights LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Putra Heights station, the last southbound train departs at -, the last northbound train departs at 2320H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Gombak",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Gombak LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Gombak station, the last southbound train departs at 2317H, the last northbound train departs at -, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Melati",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Melati LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taman Melati station, the last southbound train departs at 2320H, the last northbound train departs at 2412H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Wangsa Maju",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Wangsa Maju LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Wangsa Maju station, the last southbound train departs at 2323H, the last northbound train departs at 2409H, and the ticket counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sri Rampai",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Sri Rampai LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Sri Rampai station, the last southbound train departs at 2325H, the last northbound train departs at 2407H, and the ticket counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Setiawangsa",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Setiawangsa LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Setiawangsa station, the last southbound train departs at 2329H, the last northbound train departs at 2403H, and the ticket counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Jelatek",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Jelatek LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Jelatek station, the last southbound train departs at 2331H, the last northbound train departs at 2401H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Dato' Keramat",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Dato' Keramat LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Dato' Keramat station, the last southbound train departs at 2333H, the last northbound train departs at 2359H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Damai",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Damai LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Damai station, the last southbound train departs at 2335H, the last northbound train departs at 2357H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Ampang Park",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Ampang Park LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Ampang Park station, the last southbound train departs at 2337H, the last northbound train departs at 2355H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "KLCC",
    "question": "What are the last train times at KLCC LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at KLCC station, the last southbound train departs at 2339H, the last northbound train departs at 2353H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kampung Baru",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kampung Baru LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Kampung Baru station, the last southbound train departs at 2341H, the last northbound train departs at 2351H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Dang Wangi",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Dang Wangi LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Dang Wangi station, the last southbound train departs at 2343H, the last northbound train departs at 2349H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Masjid Jamek",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Masjid Jamek LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Masjid Jamek station, the last southbound train departs at 2345H, the last northbound train departs at 2347H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Pasar Seni",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Pasar Seni LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Pasar Seni station, the last southbound train departs at 2347H, the last northbound train departs at 2345H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "KL Sentral",
    "question": "What are the last train times at KL Sentral LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at KL Sentral station, the last southbound train departs at 2350H, the last northbound train departs at 2342H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bangsar",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bangsar LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Bangsar station, the last southbound train departs at 2352H, the last northbound train departs at 2340H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Abdullah Hukum",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Abdullah Hukum LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Abdullah Hukum station, the last southbound train departs at 2354H, the last northbound train departs at 2338H, and the ticket counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kerinchi",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kerinchi LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Kerinchi station, the last southbound train departs at 2356H, the last northbound train departs at 2336H, and the ticket counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Universiti",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Universiti LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Universiti station, the last southbound train departs at 2358H, the last northbound train departs at 2334H, and the ticket counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Jaya LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taman Jaya station, the last southbound train departs at 2401H, the last northbound train departs at 2331H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Asia Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Asia Jaya LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Asia Jaya station, the last southbound train departs at 2403H, the last northbound train departs at 2329H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Paramount",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Paramount LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taman Paramount station, the last southbound train departs at 2405H, the last northbound train departs at 2327H, and the ticket counter closes at 2310H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Bahagia",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Bahagia LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taman Bahagia station, the last southbound train departs at 2407H, the last northbound train departs at 2325H, and the ticket counter closes at 2310H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kelana Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kelana Jaya LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Kelana Jaya station, the last southbound train departs at 2410H, the last northbound train departs at 2322H, and the ticket counter closes at 2310H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Lembah Subang",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Lembah Subang LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Lembah Subang station, the last southbound train departs at 2413H, the last northbound train departs at 2319H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Ara Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Ara Damansara LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Ara Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2415H, the last northbound train departs at 2317H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Glenmarie",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Glenmarie LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Glenmarie station, the last southbound train departs at 2417H, the last northbound train departs at 2315H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Subang Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Subang Jaya LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Subang Jaya station, the last southbound train departs at 2420H, the last northbound train departs at 2312H, and the ticket counter closes at 2300H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "SS 15",
    "question": "What are the last train times at SS 15 LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at SS 15 station, the last southbound train departs at 2423H, the last northbound train departs at 2309H, and the ticket counter closes at 2300H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "SS 18",
    "question": "What are the last train times at SS 18 LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at SS 18 station, the last southbound train departs at 2425H, the last northbound train departs at 2307H, and the ticket counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "USJ 7",
    "question": "What are the last train times at USJ 7 LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at USJ 7 station, the last southbound train departs at 2429H, the last northbound train departs at 2303H, and the ticket counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taipan",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taipan LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taipan station, the last southbound train departs at 2431H, the last northbound train departs at 2301H, and the ticket counter closes at 2250H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Wawasan",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Wawasan LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Wawasan station, the last southbound train departs at 2433H, the last northbound train departs at 2259H, and the ticket counter closes at 2250H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "USJ 21",
    "question": "What are the last train times at USJ 21 LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at USJ 21 station, the last southbound train departs at 2435H, the last northbound train departs at 2257H, and the ticket counter closes at 2250H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Alam Megah",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Alam Megah LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Alam Megah station, the last southbound train departs at 2438H, the last northbound train departs at 2254H, and the ticket counter closes at 2245H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Subang Alam",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Subang Alam LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Subang Alam station, the last southbound train departs at 2440H, the last northbound train departs at 2252H, and the ticket counter closes at 2245H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Putra Heights",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Putra Heights LRT Kelana Jaya Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Putra Heights station, the last southbound train departs at -, the last northbound train departs at 2250H, and the ticket counter closes at 2245H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kwasa Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kwasa Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Kwasa Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2336H, the last northbound train departs at -, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kwasa Sentral",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kwasa Sentral MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Kwasa Sentral station, the last southbound train departs at 2339H, the last northbound train departs at 2449H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kota Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kota Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Kota Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2342H, the last northbound train departs at 2445H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Surian",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Surian MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Surian station, the last southbound train departs at 2344H, the last northbound train departs at 2443H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Mutiara Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Mutiara Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Mutiara Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2347H, the last northbound train departs at 2440H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandar Utama",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bandar Utama MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Bandar Utama station, the last southbound train departs at 2349H, the last northbound train departs at 2437H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "TTDI",
    "question": "What are the last train times at TTDI MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at TTDI station, the last southbound train departs at 2352H, the last northbound train departs at 2434H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Phileo Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Phileo Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Phileo Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2354H, the last northbound train departs at 2432H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Pusat Bandar Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Pusat Bandar Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Pusat Bandar Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2357H, the last northbound train departs at 2428H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Semantan",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Semantan MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Semantan station, the last southbound train departs at 2400H, the last northbound train departs at 2425H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Muzium Negara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Muzium Negara MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Muzium Negara station, the last southbound train departs at 2404H, the last northbound train departs at 2420H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Pasar Seni",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Pasar Seni MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Pasar Seni station, the last southbound train departs at 2406H, the last northbound train departs at 2418H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Merdeka",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Merdeka MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Merdeka station, the last southbound train departs at 2408H, the last northbound train departs at 2416H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bukit Bintang",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bukit Bintang MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Bukit Bintang station, the last southbound train departs at 2411H, the last northbound train departs at 2413H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Tun Razak Exchange",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Tun Razak Exchange MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Tun Razak Exchange station, the last southbound train departs at 2413H, the last northbound train departs at 2410H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Cochrane",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Cochrane MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Cochrane station, the last southbound train departs at 2416H, the last northbound train departs at 2408H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Maluri",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Maluri MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Maluri station, the last southbound train departs at 2418H, the last northbound train departs at 2406H, and the ticket counter closes at 2400H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Pertama",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Pertama MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taman Pertama station, the last southbound train departs at 2421H, the last northbound train departs at 2402H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Midah",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Midah MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taman Midah station, the last southbound train departs at 2423H, the last northbound train departs at 2400H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Mutiara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Mutiara MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taman Mutiara station, the last southbound train departs at 2425H, the last northbound train departs at 2358H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Connaught",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Connaught MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taman Connaught station, the last southbound train departs at 2427H, the last northbound train departs at 2356H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Suntex",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Suntex MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Taman Suntex station, the last southbound train departs at 2430H, the last northbound train departs at 2353H, and the ticket counter closes at 2345H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sri Raya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Sri Raya MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Sri Raya station, the last southbound train departs at 2433H, the last northbound train departs at 2350H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandar Tun Hussein Onn",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bandar Tun Hussein Onn MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Bandar Tun Hussein Onn station, the last southbound train departs at 2435H, the last northbound train departs at 2348H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Batu 11 Cheras",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Batu 11 Cheras MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Batu 11 Cheras station, the last southbound train departs at 2437H, the last northbound train departs at 2346H, and the ticket counter closes at 2335H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bukit Dukung",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bukit Dukung MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Bukit Dukung station, the last southbound train departs at 2440H, the last northbound train departs at 2343H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sungai Jernih",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Sungai Jernih MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Sungai Jernih station, the last southbound train departs at 2443H, the last northbound train departs at 2340H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Stadium Kajang",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Stadium Kajang MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Stadium Kajang station, the last southbound train departs at 2445H, the last northbound train departs at 2338H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kajang",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kajang MRT Kajang Line station on Monday to Saturday?",
    "answer": "On Monday to Saturday at Kajang station, the last southbound train departs at -, the last northbound train departs at 2335H, and the ticket counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kwasa Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kwasa Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Kwasa Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2306H, the last northbound train departs at -, and the ticket counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kwasa Sentral",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kwasa Sentral MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Kwasa Sentral station, the last southbound train departs at 2308H, the last northbound train departs at 2416H, and the ticket counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kota Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kota Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Kota Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2312H, the last northbound train departs at 2413H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Surian",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Surian MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Surian station, the last southbound train departs at 2314H, the last northbound train departs at 2410H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Mutiara Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Mutiara Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Mutiara Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2316H, the last northbound train departs at 2407H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandar Utama",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bandar Utama MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Bandar Utama station, the last southbound train departs at 2319H, the last northbound train departs at 2405H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "TTDI",
    "question": "What are the last train times at TTDI MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at TTDI station, the last southbound train departs at 2322H, the last northbound train departs at 2402H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Phileo Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Phileo Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Phileo Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2324H, the last northbound train departs at 2359H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Pusat Bandar Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Pusat Bandar Damansara MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Pusat Bandar Damansara station, the last southbound train departs at 2328H, the last northbound train departs at 2355H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Semantan",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Semantan MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Semantan station, the last southbound train departs at 2330H, the last northbound train departs at 2353H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Muzium Negara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Muzium Negara MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Muzium Negara station, the last southbound train departs at 2335H, the last northbound train departs at 2349H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Pasar Seni",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Pasar Seni MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Pasar Seni station, the last southbound train departs at 2337H, the last northbound train departs at 2346H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Merdeka",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Merdeka MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Merdeka station, the last southbound train departs at 2339H, the last northbound train departs at 2344H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bukit Bintang",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bukit Bintang MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Bukit Bintang station, the last southbound train departs at 2342H, the last northbound train departs at 2342H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Tun Razak Exchange",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Tun Razak Exchange MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Tun Razak Exchange station, the last southbound train departs at 2344H, the last northbound train departs at 2339H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Cochrane",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Cochrane MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Cochrane station, the last southbound train departs at 2346H, the last northbound train departs at 2337H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Maluri",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Maluri MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Maluri station, the last southbound train departs at 2349H, the last northbound train departs at 2335H, and the ticket counter closes at 2330H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Pertama",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Pertama MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taman Pertama station, the last southbound train departs at 2352H, the last northbound train departs at 2331H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Midah",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Midah MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taman Midah station, the last southbound train departs at 2354H, the last northbound train departs at 2329H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Mutiara",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Mutiara MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taman Mutiara station, the last southbound train departs at 2356H, the last northbound train departs at 2327H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Connaught",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Connaught MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taman Connaught station, the last southbound train departs at 2359H, the last northbound train departs at 2324H, and the ticket counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Suntex",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Taman Suntex MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Taman Suntex station, the last southbound train departs at 2402H, the last northbound train departs at 2321H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sri Raya",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Sri Raya MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Sri Raya station, the last southbound train departs at 2404H, the last northbound train departs at 2319H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandar Tun Hussein Onn",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bandar Tun Hussein Onn MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Bandar Tun Hussein Onn station, the last southbound train departs at 2406H, the last northbound train departs at 2317H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Batu 11 Cheras",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Batu 11 Cheras MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Batu 11 Cheras station, the last southbound train departs at 2408H, the last northbound train departs at 2315H, and the ticket counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bukit Dukung",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Bukit Dukung MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Bukit Dukung station, the last southbound train departs at 2410H, the last northbound train departs at 2313H, and the ticket counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sungai Jernih",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Sungai Jernih MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Sungai Jernih station, the last southbound train departs at 2414H, the last northbound train departs at 2309H, and the ticket counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Stadium Kajang",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Stadium Kajang MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Stadium Kajang station, the last southbound train departs at 2415H, the last northbound train departs at 2307H, and the ticket counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kajang",
    "question": "What are the last train times at Kajang MRT Kajang Line station on Sundays and public holidays?",
    "answer": "On Sundays and public holidays at Kajang station, the last southbound train departs at -, the last northbound train departs at 2305H, and the ticket counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kwasa Damansara",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Kwasa Damansara station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2336H and there is no northbound service. Counter closes at 2330H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2300H and there is no northbound service. Counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kampung Selamat",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Kampung Selamat station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2339H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2454H. Counter closes at 2330H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2303H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2426H. Counter closes at 2255H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sungai Buloh",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sungai Buloh station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2341H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2450H. Counter closes at 2330H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2305H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2424H. Counter closes at 2300H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Damansara Damai",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Damansara Damai station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2344H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2448H. Counter closes at 2335H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2307H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2422H. Counter closes at 2300H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sri Damansara Barat",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sri Damansara Barat station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2347H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2445H. Counter closes at 2335H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2310H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2420H. Counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sri Damansara Sentral",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sri Damansara Sentral station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2349H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2443H. Counter closes at 2340H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2312H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2419H. Counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sri Damansara Timur",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sri Damansara Timur station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2352H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2441H. Counter closes at 2340H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2314H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2416H. Counter closes at 2310H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Serdang Raya Utara",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Serdang Raya Utara station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2438H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2355H. Counter closes at 2345H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2409H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2325H. Counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Serdang Raya Selatan",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Serdang Raya Selatan station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2440H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2353H. Counter closes at 2340H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2411H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2323H. Counter closes at 2320H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Serdang Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Serdang Jaya station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2442H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2350H. Counter closes at 2340H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2413H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2321H. Counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "UPM",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at UPM station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2444H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2351H. Counter closes at 2335H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2414H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2320H. Counter closes at 2315H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Equine",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Taman Equine station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2447H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2345H. Counter closes at 2335H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2417H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2317H. Counter closes at 2310H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Putra Permai",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Putra Permai station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2451H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2341H. Counter closes at 2335H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2419H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2315H. Counter closes at 2310H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "16 Sierra",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at 16 Sierra station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2454H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2339H. Counter closes at 2330H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2421H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2313H. Counter closes at 2305H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Cyberjaya Utara",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Cyberjaya Utara station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2457H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2337H. Counter closes at 2330H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2424H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2310H. Counter closes at 2300H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Cyberjaya City Centre",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Cyberjaya City Centre station on the Putrajaya Line?",
    "answer": "On weekdays (Monday to Saturday), the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2458H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2336H. Counter closes at 2330H. On Sundays and public holidays, the last train towards Putrajaya Sentral is at 2427H and the last train towards Kwasa Damansara is at 2307H. Counter closes at 2300H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sentul Timur",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sentul Timur station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2349H (counter closes at 2345H). There is no service towards Sentul Timur as it is the terminal station. The last northbound service ends at 2433H (counter closes at 2433H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sentul",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sentul station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2351H (counter closes at 2346H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2437H (counter closes at 2432H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Titiwangsa",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Titiwangsa station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2352H (counter closes at 2347H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2436H (counter closes at 2431H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "PWTC",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at PWTC station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2354H (counter closes at 2349H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2434H (counter closes at 2429H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sultan Ismail",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sultan Ismail station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2355H (counter closes at 2351H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2433H (counter closes at 2428H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandaraya",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Bandaraya station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2358H (counter closes at 2353H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2431H (counter closes at 2426H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Masjid Jamek",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Masjid Jamek station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2400H (counter closes at 2355H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2428H (counter closes at 2423H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Plaza Rakyat",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Plaza Rakyat station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2402H (counter closes at 2357H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2425H (counter closes at 2420H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Hang Tuah",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Hang Tuah station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2405H (counter closes at 2400H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2423H (counter closes at 2418H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Pudu",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Pudu station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2407H (counter closes at 2402H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2420H (counter closes at 2415H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Chan Sow Lin",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Chan Sow Lin station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2409H (counter closes at 2404H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2418H (counter closes at 2413H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Cheras",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Cheras station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2412H (counter closes at 2407H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2415H (counter closes at 2411H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Salak Selatan",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Salak Selatan station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2414H (counter closes at 2408H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2413H (counter closes at 2408H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandar Tun Razak",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Bandar Tun Razak station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2416H (counter closes at 2406H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2411H (counter closes at 2406H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandar Tasik Selatan",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Bandar Tasik Selatan station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2419H (counter closes at 2404H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2409H (counter closes at 2404H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sungai Besi",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sungai Besi station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2423H (counter closes at 2400H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2405H (counter closes at 2400H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bukit Jalil",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Bukit Jalil station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2428H (counter closes at 2354H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2359H (counter closes at 2354H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sri Petaling",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sri Petaling station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2431H (counter closes at 2352H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2357H (counter closes at 2352H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Awan Besar",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Awan Besar station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2433H (counter closes at 2349H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2354H (counter closes at 2349H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Muhibbah",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Muhibbah station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2435H (counter closes at 2347H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2352H (counter closes at 2347H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Alam Sutera",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Alam Sutera station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2437H (counter closes at 2345H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2350H (counter closes at 2345H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Kinrara BK5",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Kinrara BK5 station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2439H (counter closes at 2343H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2348H (counter closes at 2343H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "IOI Puchong Jaya",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at IOI Puchong Jaya station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2443H (counter closes at 2339H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2344H (counter closes at 2339H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Pusat Bandar Puchong",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Pusat Bandar Puchong station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2445H (counter closes at 2337H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2342H (counter closes at 2337H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Taman Perindustrian Puchong",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Taman Perindustrian Puchong station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2447H (counter closes at 2335H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2340H (counter closes at 2335H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandar Puteri",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Bandar Puteri station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2449H (counter closes at 2334H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2339H (counter closes at 2334H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Puchong Perdana",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Puchong Perdana station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2451H (counter closes at 2331H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2336H (counter closes at 2331H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Puchong Prima",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Puchong Prima station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Putra Heights is at 2454H (counter closes at 2328H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2333H (counter closes at 2328H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Putra Heights",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Putra Heights station on the Sri Petaling Line?",
    "answer": "There is no southbound service. The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2330H. Counter closes at 2325H."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sentul Timur",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sentul Timur station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2330H (counter closes at 2325H). There is no northbound service from Sentul Timur."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sentul",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sentul station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2333H (counter closes at 2328H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2355H (counter closes at 2350H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Titiwangsa",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Titiwangsa station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2336H (counter closes at 2331H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2352H (counter closes at 2347H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "PWTC",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at PWTC station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2338H (counter closes at 2329H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2350H (counter closes at 2345H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sultan Ismail",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sultan Ismail station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2340H (counter closes at 2328H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2348H (counter closes at 2343H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Majlis Jamek",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Masjid Jamek station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2343H (counter closes at 2326H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2346H (counter closes at 2341H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandaraya",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Bandaraya station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2345H (counter closes at 2324H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2344H (counter closes at 2339H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Hang Tuah",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Hang Tuah station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2347H (counter closes at 2322H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2342H (counter closes at 2337H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Pudu",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Pudu station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2349H (counter closes at 2320H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2340H (counter closes at 2335H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Chan Sow Lin",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Chan Sow Lin station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2351H (counter closes at 2318H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2338H (counter closes at 2333H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Cheras",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Cheras station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2353H (counter closes at 2316H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2336H (counter closes at 2331H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Salak Selatan",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Salak Selatan station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2355H (counter closes at 2314H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2334H (counter closes at 2329H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandar Tun Razak",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Bandar Tun Razak station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2357H (counter closes at 2312H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2332H (counter closes at 2327H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bandar Tasik Selatan",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Bandar Tasik Selatan station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2359H (counter closes at 2310H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2330H (counter closes at 2325H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sungai Besi",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sungai Besi station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2401H (counter closes at 2308H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2328H (counter closes at 2323H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Bukit Jalil",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Bukit Jalil station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2403H (counter closes at 2306H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2326H (counter closes at 2321H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Sri Petaling",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Sri Petaling station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Ampang is at 2405H (counter closes at 2304H). The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2324H (counter closes at 2319H)."
  },
  {
    "topic": "Closing",
    "station": "Ampang",
    "question": "What are the last train times and counter closing times at Ampang station on the Ampang Line?",
    "answer": "The last train towards Sentul Timur is at 2320H (counter closes at 2315H). There is no southbound service from Ampang."
  }
]

